ecorevenue.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy policy

Below you can read the conditions of the Privacy Policy where, subject to the requirements of the Republic of Poland, the information about collection of data, including your personal data in connection with the Services provided by Recyclix Sp.z o.o. that has a status of a payer of tax on income on a regular basis in accordance with the Tax Code of the Republic of Poland (REGON 360290387, NIP 5272725464, KRS 0000533282, Województwo MAZOWIECKIE, Powiat m. st. Warszawa, Gmina Wola, miejscowość WARSZAWA, ulica ALEJA "SOLIDARNOŚCI", nr domu 115, nr lokalu 2, kod pocztowy 00-140, poczta WARSZAWA, kraj POLSKA), as well as about their processing is presented. Acceptance of the Terms of Use located on http://recyclix.com means your compliance with the conditions indicated in this Privacy Policy.

Recyclix Sp.z o.o. lays special emphasis on protection of the private life of the Users of the Services and security of processing of their personal data. Services of personal data processing that are featured in registration forms as well as personal data collected automatically are processed in compliance with the conditions of the Law from August 29, 1997, about the protection of the personal data (USTAWA z dnia 29 sierpnia 1997 r. o ochronie danych osobowych) and the Law from July 18, 2002, about provision of the electronic services (USTAWA z dnia 18 lipca 2002 r. o świadczeniu usług drogą elektroniczną), inclusive of the current alterations and annexe. The Users have the right for access to their personal data and are entitled to editing them. The data that are collected automatically cannot be altered or erased by the Users of the Website.

## I. Data collection

1\. Data specified by the User, including the personal data of the User

The User is asked to provide certain information upon registration, including his or her personal information upon his or her consent. Your personal information featured in the registration forms on the Website will be processed solely in accordance with this Privacy Policy for provision of services provided by the Website as well as for purposes specified in the registration forms of the corresponding services on the Website. Apart from it, these data may only be processed upon the consent of the User and solely for lawful purposes, including the purposes of direct marketing of the Services, Products, Policy of the Company as well as third-party companies that collaborate with Recyclix Sp.z o.o.

## II. Data privacy

1\. Recyclix Sp.z o.o. do not trade or exchange (neither sale nor lease) the personal information of the Users of the Website with third-parties without their consent. The personal data of the Users of the Website may be accessed SOLELY by the authorized government bodies and SOLELY upon the authorized request for investigation purposes as well as third-parties that act according to the authorized written and personal requests given by the government bodies in cases when these third-parties act on behalf of such government bodies. These are the law requirements and we shall comply with them.

2\. Recyclix Sp.z o.o. automatically collects user information about the IP addresses of the Users of the Website and the Users of the Services provided by the Website. Data collected in such way and the results of their periodic analysis, including statistic analysis, are used for estimating the functionality of the Website and the Services. The data about the IP addresses of the Users of the Website may be accessed SOLELY by the authorized government bodies and SOLELY upon the authorized request for investigation purposes as well as third-parties that act according to the authorized written and personal requests given by the government bodies in cases when these third-parties act on behalf of such government bodies. These are the law requirements and we shall comply with them.

## III. Cookies

1\. The Website uses Cookies, which are text files that are stored in the services of your PC or any other device, using which you access the Website and use the Services.

2\. Cookies are not used for obtaining any kind of information about separate Users. They are used for authentication of the Users, storing their customized settings and preferences, recording the state and length of the user session, keeping the log and statistics, optimization of the ads on the Website, if any, as well as improvement of the work of the Website in accordance with the current standards of the WWW. Cookies can also be used if the Company collaborates with advertising services, Internet research and statistics services, and suppliers of multimedia applications.

3\. By using the tools available in the settings of any of the browser available on the market, you can any moment change the settings associated with Cookies and other technologies used for storing of the data (including Local Storage technology) in the privacy settings of your browser, particularly by automatically blocking their usage in the settings of your browser or browser plug-ins or, depending on the tools and technologies used, by displaying the detailed report about your device every time upon entering the Website as the end user. Detailed information about capabilities and usage of Cookies is featured in the settings of your browser or browser plug-ins. Making changes in these settings may lead to certain difficulties in usage of the Services or certain parts of the Services.

## IV. Links

1\. The website may include links to third-party websites and Recyclix Sp.z o.o. shall not be held responsible for the privacy policy of such third-party websites.

2\. Recyclix Sp.z o.o. also provides access to the applications offered by third-party companies. Information collected by Recyclix Sp.z o.o. after such applications came into action is processed in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Information gathered by the suppliers of such applications is processed in accordance with the privacy policy of such suppliers or other third-party companies.

## V. Communications

1\. Recyclix Sp.z o.o. may collect and store user logs for purposes of communications with the Users. Recyclix Sp.z o.o. may gather and store information about the email address or phone number/s of the User including messages, date, and time of the communications, process data, and results of the communications.

2\. Upon communication with the Users via phone, email, and so on, Recyclix Sp.z o.o. may ask the User for certain personal data like his or her name, email address and other personal data associated with the fact of the communication. Such information shall be used solely for purposes of providing the User technical support, answers to his or her questions, or information that he or she requested.

## VI. Other use

1\. Recyclix Sp.z o.o. may use the collected data for purposes of:

(а) development of new functionality as well as for improvement of the Services;

(b) development of new Services;

(с) protecting the rights of Recyclix Sp.z o.o.;

(d) execution of legitimate aims, pursued by Recyclix Sp.z o.o. or authorized third-parties that receive the data, if the processing of these data does not go against the rights and/or freedoms of the owner of the data, if necessary.

## VII. Rights of the users for personal data

1\. Recyclix Sp.z o.o. provides the Users the right to enforce their rights upon transfer of the personal data in accordance with the law from August 29, 1997, on protection of the personal data, including the rights of demanding the completeness, relevance, editing, short-term or permanent suspension of their processing or complete deletion of the personal data in case they were incorrect or collected in contravention of the law or not necessary any more for the purposes they were collected for. You have the right to delete your personal data any moment. In case if you consider that the methods of enforcing your rights are too fewer, please send a writing request to Recyclix Sp.z o.o.

## VIII. Personal data security

1\. Recyclix Sp.z o.o. uses technical and organizational means aimed at maintaining the highest standards of security and protection of the personal data of the Users from their unauthorized access or incorrect usage by any third-parties. The technical means are updated together with development of new technologies and needs as well as available means of protection.

2\. Applied organizational means guarantee that access to your personal data is granted solely to authorized persons from Recyclix Sp.z o.o. Recyclix Sp.z o.o. carries out regular checks of abidance to the corresponding laws and this Privacy Policy. Recyclix Sp.z o.o. collaborates with governmental bodies that are responsible for monitoring of collection and processing of the personal data and is ready to execute their requirements if there are any.

## IX. Amendments in this Privacy Policy

1\. Development of technology makes it inevitable not to make amendments in this Privacy Policy. You can always get familiar with the latest version of the Terms of Use any moment over here.

2\. We reserve the right to update and make amendments in the conditions of the Services by publishing the updated material here. We recommend you to check this Privacy Policy from time to time in order to get familiar with the updated conditions that may or may not influence you.

## X. Additional information

1\. If you have any questions or issues associated with this Privacy Policy, Recyclix Sp.z o.o. asks you to get in touch with it using the email address located on the contacts page on the Website.

This site require cookies to work, learn more. By visiting it you agree with our use of cookies. __  I Agree
